Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers 1966-2000 MSS 156
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Last name, First name
    - Coualt, A., undated (Box 6, Folder 684)
    - Davis, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 685)
    - Dean, Kentley Benson, undated (Box 6, Folder 686)
    - Denny, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 687)
    - Dixon, Jo, undated (Box 6, Folder 688)
    - Douksza, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 689)
    - Fend, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 690)
    - Fridley, Joanne, undated (Box 6, Folder 691)
    - Garvin, Mary, undated (Box 6, Folder 692)
    - Geller, Matthew, undated (Box 6, Folder 693)
    - Greenwood, Martha, undated (Box 6, Folder 694)
    - Haggerty, Beth, undated (Box 6, Folder 695)
    - Haskes, undated (Box 6, Folder 696)
    - Heavenrich, Ned, undated (Box 6, Folder 697)
    - Heyward, Julia, undated (Box 6, Folder 698)
    - Howland, Rebecca, undated (Box 6, Folder 699)
    - Hughes, Danne, undated (Box 6, Folder 700)
    - Hughes, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 701)
    - Huttinger, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 702)
    - Jacobs, Joyce Ringle, undated (Box 6, Folder 703)
    - Johnson, Trishia, undated (Box 6, Folder 704)
    - Kammer, Prexy, undated (Box 6, Folder 705)
    - Keeton, Darra, undated (Box 6, Folder 706)
    - Kladzyle, Pam, undated (Box 6, Folder 707)
    - Klein, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 708)
    - Klein, Harriette, undated (Box 6, Folder 709)
    - Knox, Dede, undated (Box 6, Folder 710)
    - Krughoff, Fred, undated (Box 6, Folder 711)
    - Leune, Caidyl, undated (Box 6, Folder 712)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, undated (Box 6, Folder 713)
    - McMahon, Jeff, undated (Box 6, Folder 714)
    - Martin, Patty [Mrs. Hartschorn], undated (Box 6, Folder 715)
    - Matusak, Zack, undated (Box 6, Folder 716)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated (Box 6, Folder 717)
    - Messner and Moenig, undated (Box 6, Folder 718)
    - Messner, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 719)
    - Miller, Barb, undated (Box 6, Folder 720)
    - Mock, Richard and Patti, undated (Box 6, Folder 721)
    - Mullin, Molly, undated (Box 6, Folder 722)
    - Nathan, Gail, undated (Box 6, Folder 723)
    - Nichols, Dr. Alice, undated (Box 6, Folder 724)
    - Nolan, Janet, undated (Box 6, Folder 725)
    - O'Neill, Bonnie, undated (Box 6, Folder 726)
    - Passera, Bill, undated (Box 6, Folder 727)
    - Payne, Sandra, undated (Box 6, Folder 728)
    - Peckman, Glen, undated (Box 6, Folder 729)
    - Perlman, Cara, undated (Box 6, Folder 730)
    - Petior, Anna, undated (Box 6, Folder 731)
    - Potter, Janet, undated (Box 6, Folder 732)
    - Provincial Museum at Hasselt, undated (Box 6, Folder 733)
    - Rees, Sarah, undated (Box 6, Folder 734)
    - Reynolds, Jock, undated (Box 6, Folder 735)
    - Romeu, Joost, undated (Box 6, Folder 736)
    - Rubin, Bernice, undated (Box 6, Folder 737)
    - Rupp, Christy, undated (Box 6, Folder 738)
    - Roddy, D.S., undated (Box 6, Folder 739)
    - Saret, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 740)
    - Segerr, Nan, undated (Box 6, Folder 741)
    - Seltman, Robert L., undated (Box 7, Folder 742)
    - Siegle, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 743)
    - Slotkin, Terry, undated (Box 7, Folder 744)
    - Smagula, Howard, undated (Box 7, Folder 745)
    - Smith, Bob, undated (Box 7, Folder 746)
    - Smith, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 747)
    - Snyder, Molly, undated (Box 7, Folder 748)
    - Staten, Pat, undated (Box 7, Folder 749)
    - Stevens, May, undated (Box 7, Folder 750)
    - Stoltz, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 751)
    - Trapnell, Baylor, undated (Box 7, Folder 752)
    - Vincent, Jim, undated (Box 7, Folder 753)
    - Vincent, Kitty, undated (Box 7, Folder 754)
    - Vukos, Jim, undated (Box 7, Folder 755)
    - Ward, B., undated (Box 7, Folder 756)
    - Wellman, Jerry, undated (Box 7, Folder 757)
    - Wilde, Betty [Bronx River Restoration], undated (Box 7, Folder 758)
    - Williams, Carol [also known as Winefred and Carol Gordon], undated (Box 7, Folder 759)
    - Williams, Reese, undated (Box 7, Folder 760)
    - Wilson, Martha Redy Story, undated (Box 7, Folder 761)
    - Winkleman, Harriet, undated (Box 7, Folder 762)
    - Wolff, Whitney, undated (Box 7, Folder 763)
    - Wornsy, Al, undated (Box 7, Folder 764)
    - Youngblood, Daisy, undated (Box 7, Folder 765)
  - Subseries B: First name
    - Allen, undated (Box 7, Folder 766)
    - Ann, undated (Box 7, Folder 767)
    - Beckie, undated (Box 7, Folder 768)
    - Bill, undated (Box 7, Folder 769)
    - Carrina, undated (Box 7, Folder 770)
    - Chris, undated (Box 7, Folder 771)
    - Clarissa, undated (Box 7, Folder 772)
    - Dennis, undated (Box 7, Folder 773)
    - E.W.H., undated (Box 7, Folder 774)
    - Harriet Z., undated (Box 7, Folder 775)
    - Irene, undated (Box 7, Folder 776)
    - Jane, undated (Box 7, Folder 777)
    - Jean [aunt], undated (Box 7, Folder 778)
    - Josh, undated (Box 7, Folder 779)
    - Kris and Char, undated (Box 7, Folder 780)
    - Laura, undated (Box 7, Folder 781)
    - Larry, undated (Box 7, Folder 782)
    - Liana, Zara and Jon, undated (Box 7, Folder 783)
    - Marietta, undated (Box 7, Folder 784)
    - Mark, undated (Box 7, Folder 785)
    - MEB, undated (Box 7, Folder 786)
    - Meg, undated (Box 7, Folder 787)
    - Mindy, undated (Box 7, Folder 788)
    - Mother, undated (Box 7, Folder 789)
    - Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 790)
    - Otis B., undated (Box 7, Folder 791)
    - Pam, undated (Box 7, Folder 792)
    - Pamela, undated (Box 7, Folder 793)
    - Pat, undated (Box 7, Folder 794)
    - Ralph, undated (Box 7, Folder 795)
    - Randi and Mark, undated (Box 7, Folder 796)
    - Red, undated (Box 7, Folder 797)
    - Rose, undated (Box 7, Folder 798)
    - Ruby, undated (Box 7, Folder 799)
    - Ruth, undated (Box 7, Folder 800)
    - Ruth C., undated (Box 7, Folder 801)
    - Scott, undated (Box 7, Folder 802)
    - Sheila, undated (Box 7, Folder 803)
    - Sophie, undated (Box 7, Folder 804)
    - Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 805)
    - Suzanne, undated (Box 7, Folder 806)
    - T., undated (Box 7, Folder 807)
    - T.B., undated (Box 7, Folder 808)
  - Subseries C: From Andrea Callard
    - Dad, undated (Box 7, Folder 809)
    - James, undated (Box 7, Folder 810)
    - Joe and Claudio, undated (Box 7, Folder 811)
    - Joost Romeu, undated (Box 7, Folder 812)
    - Pat, undated (Box 7, Folder 813)
    - Kitty and Jim Pearson Vincent, undated (Box 7, Folder 814)
    - Reese and Carol Williams, undated (Box 7, Folder 815)
    - Reese Williams, undated (Box 7, Folder 816)
    - unknown, undated (Box 7, Folder 817)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - Addresses and contact information, undated (Box 7, Folder 818)
    - Unlabeled or illegible correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 819)
    - Miscellaneous mail from businesses, undated (Box 7, Folder 820)
    - Correspondence from others to others [i.e. from Reese Williams to Mark, undated (Box 7, Folder 821)
- Series VI: Biographical
  This series contains materials related to Andrea Callard's childhood, personal photographs and snapshots as well as personal reflective writing such as dream journals. Materials are arranged in chronological order with undated materials at the end of the series.
  - Membership cards, 1966-1979 (Box 7, Folder 822)
  - Photograph of Andrea Callard's house at Cranbrook, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 823)
  - Citizenship Award from Kingswood School Cranbrook student council, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 824)
  - Indianapolis 500 ticket, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 825)
  - Callard photograph of Robin Winters, Laurie Binder, Baylor Trapnell on vacation together in Maine, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 826)
  - Personal Notes to self, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 827)
  - Dreams, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 828)
  - Dreams, Plans and other notes, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 829)
  - Miscellaneous writing, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 830)
  - letter information occurence, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 831)
  - Materials removed from Distance Fool by Gary Brown, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 832)
  - McBarney YMCA yoga class, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 833)
  - Candid color snapshots, Andrea Callard, Fred Krughoff, the Vincents, and the Williams, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 834)
  - Andrea Callard and Matthew Geller in the Berkshires, 26 color slides, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 835)
  - Color slides, sailing school, 12 color slides, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 836)
  - Cherry Valley Sulivan County House, rented with Gail Nathan. Color slides. 56 color slides, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 837)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, unlabeled and ungrouped. Mostly snapshots, undated (Box 7, Folder 838)
  - Kingswood School Cranbrook alumni magazine. Andrea Callard wrote the section for her year, undated (Box 7, Folder 839)
  - Color snapshots. Wait staff at Claudios at the beach, undated (Box 7, Folder 840)
  - Word Debris [not fun], undated (Box 7, Folder 841)
  - Lists of books to read, undated (Box 7, Folder 842)
  - Souvenir slides from Galerie du Jeu Paume, undated (Box 7, Folder 843)
  - Acupuncture, undated (Box 7, Folder 845)
  - Healing, undated (Box 7, Folder 846)
  - Thoughts on Relationship with Fred, undated (Box 7, Folder 847)
  - Miscellaneous color snapshots, stacked together. Includes some of Ailanthus trees or Cynthia larvae., undated (Box Binder J, Folder a)
  - Baylor Trapnell cuts up safe at 150 Chambers St., undated (Box Binder J, Folder b)
  - Color snapshots. Includes images of Ned Heavenrich in California, Postcards from Reese and Carol Williams, Lispenard Renovation, AC and others on Staten Island Ferry, Brick City dog, Brick City and Megan. Post 1976, undated (Box Binder J, Folder c)
  - Color snaposhots. Images of the views from 40 Lispenard St, Canal St Post office. Post-1976, undated (Box Binder J, Folder d)
  - Color snaposhots. Images of the view of Lispenard St, gamblers enroute to Atlantic City, undated (Box Binder J, Folder e)
  - Color snapshots, images of the views from PS1, Andrea Callard and Cara Perlman at PS1, undated (Box Binder J, Folder f)
  - Color snapshots, images of Brook.Bridge tree, Queens from PS1 and Forsythia near NY Botanic Garden., undated (Box Binder J, Folder g)
  - color snapshot images and negatives of New York City., undated (Box Binder J, Folder h)
  - Color snapshot images of Ailanthus in NYC and editing room in studio at 40 Lispenard., undated (Box Binder J, Folder i)
  - Color snapshots "Jim and Kathy Vincent lived in my Tent Sculpture while in NY to edit film about fishin in Costa Rica", undated (Box Binder J, Folder j)
  - Color snapshots of Corinne and studio set of 11-12 film and Fred Krughoff in Florida, undated (Box Binder J, Folder k)
  - Lispenard Rennovation, undated (Box Binder J, Folder l)
  - color snapshot images of Mac Becket, Girl "plumber", Manhattan Bridge, Ed Harker, Grandmother reading Times., undated (Box Binder J, Folder m)
- Series VII: Printed Materials
  This series includes printed materials. Items are arrnaged in alphabetical order by author's last name.
  - Associated Press Stylebook, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 849)
  - Avalanche Magazine promotional callendar, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 850)
  - Brownsmead flier, undated (Box 7, Folder 851)
  - Bu Gao Ban, Chinatown History Project Newsletter, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 851A)
  - Callard, Madden and Associates: Corporate Financial Performances and Stock Prices, undated (Box 7, Folder 852)
  - A Citizen's Guide to Adirondack Park Agency Land Use Regulations, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 853)
  - Everglades informational brochure, undated (Box 7, Folder 854)
  - Gedulo, Harry. Film Makers on Film Making., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 856)
  - Geller, Suzanne. The Artist's Craft, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 857)
  - Gersten, Robert. The Spirit of Ole Bryant Lake, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 858)
  - Goldman, David. A is for OX (Box 7, Folder 859)
  - Halprin, Lawrence. The RSVP Cycles., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 860)
  - Just Another Asshole #6, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 861)
  - Key West Aloe Fragrance and Cosmetics, undated (Box 8, Folder 862)
  - Klayman, Toby Judith. The Artists' Survival Manual, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 863)
  - Lippard, Lucy. Get the Message?, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 864)
  - Malone NY, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 864A)
  - National African American Museum Project, Imagining Families: Images and Voices, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 865)
  - National Inspirer, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 866)
  - New York Public Library booklists and materials, undated (Box 8, Folder 867)
  - Official Rental Directory of Accredited Canoe liveries and outfitters, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 868)
  - Porter Cable Router instruction manual, undated (Box 8, Folder 869)
  - Postcard images, undated (Box 8, Folder 870)
  - Printed Matter, Inc. catalogue, undated (Box 8, Folder 871)
  - Public Art Fund Newsletter, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 872)
  - Real Life Magazine, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 873)
  - Smith, Mabel Parker. Greene County, New York: A Short History., undated (Box 8, Folder 875)
  - Taking Over? A Guide to eleven non-native plants that are pests in Wave Hill's woods, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 876)
  - Tanam Press Catalogue, undated (Box 8, Folder 877)
  - Thoreau, Henry David. Ktaadn, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 878)
  - Tourism Pamphlets, undated (Box 8, Folder 879)
  - Turning Leaves: The Family Albums of Two Japanese American Families, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 880)
  - USA Plant Visits 1977-1978, undated (Box 8, Folder 881)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, undated (Box 8, Folder 882)
- Series VIII: Artifacts
  This series includes objects and artifacts.
  - Red Feathered pill-box hat. Used in Red Anger polaroids, undated (Box 10)
  - Starched fabric wallet, east asian style design. In plastic packaging., undated (Box 10)
  - Kodak Super 8mm film canister, empty, undated (Box 10)
  - Ziplock bag containing film editing materials including Fuji Film splicing Tape 100, Bilora Tape-rolls, two empty film cores and canisters, two envelopse of super eight slipce tapes and a baggie containing splice fragments., undated (Box 10)
  - Mirror, black letter "A" used in "A Dressing Wall" images and "Red Anger Association"., undated (Box 11)
  - White "A" on mirror. Used in "A Dressing Wall" (Box 11)
- Series IX: Video Recordings
  Video materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Access copies may not be available for all material. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
    - Flourescent/ Azalea, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1976 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0166)
      General note
      Format: DVD, color, sound
      TRT: 00:04:00
      Original: Super 8mm film
    - 11 thru 12, a film by Andrea Callard (2009 Restoration), 1977 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0158)
      TRT: 00:11:00
    - [1]-- "11 thru 12" [2]-- "Mary Ann" [3]-- "Men In Orbit"; Co-laborative Projects June 4 Tape, [circa 1977-1980] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 156.0149)
      TRT: 01:00:32
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Title: [1]-- "11-12" [2]-- "Mary Ann" [3]-- "Men In Orbit", [circa 1977-1980] (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0001)
      Alternate title: Colaborative Projects June 4 Tape
      Credit info: [1]-- Andrea Callard [2]-- J. Holzer; J. Brettschneider [3]-- John Lurie
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Capacity: 60 minutes
      Annotations: Colaborative Projects June 4 Tape. 1.) "11-12" Andrea Callard 12 min. 2.) "Mary Ann" J. Holzer, J. Brettschneider 6 min. 3.) "Men In Orbit" John Lurie / 40 min.
    - Title: "11-12", 1977 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0002)
      Alternate title: "11 thru 12"
      Credit info: Andrea Callard
      Capacity: 20 minutes
      Annotations: "11 thru 12" Andrea Callard c. '77 // 78 MM 283 // AC Box 37 NYC 10013
    - Title: Pus Factory - MASTER, 1984 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0003)
      Alternate title: Pus Factory
      Annotations: Pus Factory -- MASTER 1984 26 sec. B+W Use black and white part of color bars. 10 secs of black between bars and beginning of tape.
    - Title: Pus Factory - DUB, 1984 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0004)
      Annotations: "Pus Factory" c. Andrea Callard 1984 B+W Silent 26 sec. + credits DUB Box 37 10013 212-925-8974
    - Title: Pus Factory - DUB, 1984 (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0005)
      Annotations: "Pus Factory" c. Callard 84 DUB 26 sec.
    - Title: Pus - Elements, [1984] (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0006)
      Alternate title:
      Credit info:
      Annotations: Callard - Pus Elements
    - Title: Notes on Ailanthus (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0007)
      Alternate title: Notes on Ailanthus - Visual Excerpts From Rough-Cut
      Annotations: Notes on Ailanthus / Visual excerpts from rough-cut. Transferred from Super-8 10 mins. (No sound) Andrea Callard Box 37 NYC 10013 925-8974-1247
    - Title: Landing #2B (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0008)
      Annotations: LANDING #2B
    - Title: Landing #1B (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0009)
      Annotations: Landing - #1B
    - Title: Moduretic, [Dub 9/2/1980] (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0010)
      Alternate title: M,S,+D "Moduretic"
      Credit info: Elaine Millaire
      Annotations: M,S,+D "Moduretic" Elaine Millaire 17:70 Dub 9/2/80 (written in pencil:) "narrator: 2 tks; 2 versions; [not vi bg]?"
    - Title: Untitled (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0011)
      Annotations: N/A
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Fragments of a Self Portrait, [circa 1975] (Box 19, Folder ID: 156.0012)
      Format: 1/2 in. Open Reel
      Capacity: [20 minutes]
      Annotations: "Drawers" 15 min. // at slip of paper...#1 "Fragments of a self-portrait." 3 1/2 min. cut. Andrea Callard 617 Tyrone Drive Mincie, Indiana 47304. (Paper bookmark w/ annotation:) "sample #2 begins"
    - Title: [Gary Brown - Cal Arts], Unknown (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0013)
      Capacity: 30 minutes. 370m., 1210 feet
      Annotations: (On cardboard sleeve:) "Gary Brown" Cal Arts
    - Title: Fragments, 1974 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0014)
      Annotations: [On container:] Callard 925-8974 Umbrellas, etc. [On reel:] Callard '74 Fragments S.P.
    - Title: Drawers - MASTER, 10/16/1975 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0015)
      Alternate title: Drawers
      Annotations: [On contaier:] Drawers (M) 16 Oct. '75 [On reel:] d. MASTER -- blank
    - Title: Bechet, Smith, A.C. '74, 1974 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0016)
      Annotations: [On reel:] Bechet, Smith, A.C. '74
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Garbage, [1]-- 1975 [2]-- Unkown (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0017)
      Annotations: Drawers // Garbage
    - Title: [1]-- Drawers [2]-- Fragments of a Self Portrait, [circa 1975] (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0018)
      Annotations: "Drawers," 15 min. Andrea Callard c. // "Fragments of a Self Porttrait" (#1, 3 1/2 min. cut) COPY
    - Title: [Cara Perlman], Unknown (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0019)
      Annotations: [On container:] Cara Perlman 40 Lispenard St. #925-1013 *start this tape at 080
    - Title: Multisensory Teaching of Reading at the Mary Mc Dowell Center for Learning, 1999 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0020)
      Format: VHS
      Capacity: 30 minutes
      Annotations: Multisensory Teaching of Reading at the Mary Mc Dowell Center for Learning, 1999. (handwritten: Return to LUKE Geller/ Andrea Callard
    - Title: Jeff McMahon 231 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0021)
      Capacity: 120 minutes
      Annotations: (taped to cassette) 231 Jeff McMahon
    - Title: Untitled (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0022)
      Annotations: (No annotations)
    - Title: Lenora Helm's Workshops (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0023)
      Annotations: Lenora Helm's Workshops
    - Title: A.C. (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0024)
      Annotations: (written on piece of masking tape on cassette:) "AC"
    - Title: Nutrition (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0025)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Nutrition
    - Title: Italian Cooking, 12/6/1992 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0026)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Italian Cooking 12/6/92
    - Title: [1]--Brooms [2]-- Willie and Luke [3]-- Sophie Dancing [4]-- My Lunch with Willie and Luke [5]-- Toys - Boat, Chairs, [1990] [1]--2/8 [2]-- 3/28 [3]-- 3/29 [4]--4/? [5]-- 6/? (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0027)
      Annotations: Feb 8 - "Brooms" Willie [Luke]; Mar 28 Willie and Luke; Mar 29 Sophie Dancing; Apr-"My Lunch with Willie and Luke" June - Toys - Boat, Chairs N. Peck
    - Title: KOBLA 12/19/02, 12/19/2002 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0028)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) KOBLA 12/19/02
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0029)
      Capacity: [15 minutes]
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp 1993 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0030)
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp 1993
    - Title: Bryant Lake Camp - Video Yearbook 1994 (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0031)
      Capacity: 10 minutes
      Annotations: (on cassette:) Bryant Lake Camp - Video Yearbook 1994
    - Title: [#1] (Box 20, Folder ID: 156.0032)
      Annotations: (on sleve:) 3 (crossed out) 1
- Series X: Audio Recordings
  Audio materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Audio access copies may not yet be available. Please check with the Fales Archivist.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Title: 2 A's Singing; Spring 1976 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0033)
      Format: 1/4 in. reel to reel
      Capacity:
      Annotations: (on container:) 2 A's Singing / '76 Spring
    - Title: A + C Sentence and Song Collection; Feb. 1, 1977, 2/1/1977 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0034)
      Annotations: (on container:) Side 1 A+C 1 Feb. '77 45 mn 71/2 Sentence and Song Collection
    - Title: A + C Sentence Collection #2, [1977] (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0035)
      Annotations: (on container:) A + C Sentence Coll #2
    - Title: Unititled, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0036)
    - Title: Songs (1), Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0037)
      Annotations: (on reel:) Songs (1)
    - Title: Lost Shoe Blues, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0038)
      Alternate title: 2 A's Singing; Spring '76
      Annotations: (on container:) Lost Shoe Blues [sung] July 5,'76 /// (on reel:) 2 A's Singing/ 76 Spring
    - Title: Bells, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0039)
      Annotations: (on container and reel:) Bells
    - Title: The Double X Corporation Menaton, 2/1974 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0040)
      Annotations: (on container:) "The Double X Corporation Menaton" [Rene] William Feb 1974 1/4 track 71/2
    - Title: Thin Waxed Beekman, 10/1974 (Box 21, Folder 156.0041A)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Thin Waxed Beekman" 10/74 R.W. 71/2 ips 1/4 track
    - Title: Life Mixing, 7/5/1975 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0042)
      Annotations: (on container:) Life Mixing 7/5/75 1/4 tr dub 3 3/4
    - Title: Your Copy, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0043)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Your Copy" 7 1/2 1/4 tr. 4 shortpieces
    - Title: "Double X": Winter Activity '74, [7/1975] (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0044)
      Annotations: (on container:) "Double X": Winter Activity '74 // Music in X pattern for Andrea (crossed out: "5/75) 7/75 7 1/2 1/4 Tr. Improvised, Buchla
    - Title: Music For Andy From Roberta For Her Quarter Century B-Day, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0045)
      Annotations: (on container:) Music For Andy From Roberta For Her Quarter Century B-Day // speed 3 3/4
    - Title: Music in Loop Patterns for Andrea 7/75, 7/1975 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0046)
      Annotations: (on container:) Music in Loop Patterns for Andrea 7/75 Side 1 with voice loop Theresa / Side two Fast, Modular, America, improvised, Buchla, 7 1/2, 1/4 track
    - Title: Untitled, Unknown (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0047)
      Annotations: (no annotations)
    - Title: Debriefing: A Reading by Susan Sontag, 5/27/1979 (Box 21, Folder ID: 156.0145)
      Format: LP
      Capacity: Unknown